<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cert on Buffor // Blog</title><link>https://vksundararajan.github.io/buffor.lol/tags/cert/</link><description>Recent content in Cert on Buffor // Blog</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://vksundararajan.github.io/buffor.lol/tags/cert/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CRTP: My Experience</title><link>https://vksundararajan.github.io/buffor.lol/blog/crtp-my-experience/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vksundararajan.github.io/buffor.lol/blog/crtp-my-experience/</guid><description>&lt;p>Hey everyone,&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I’m really happy to share that I’ve cleared the &lt;mark>CRTP (Certified Red Team Professional)&lt;/mark> exam &lt;strong>on my first attempt!&lt;/strong> This was a whole new area for me—no prior Active Directory (AD) pentesting experience, and still, I managed to get through it. So if you’re someone wondering whether this cert is possible without an AD background—yes, it is. Let me walk you through how I did it.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/628794_3744024c76874b21808fcc3765e6f663~mv2.png" alt="certified-red-team-professional-crtp">&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="my-background-before-crtp">My Background Before CRTP&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Before jumping into CRTP, my only real exposure to pentesting was TryHackMe rooms and clearing the eJPT exam. To be honest, I had never done any complete AD-based CTFs before. CRTP was the first time I was diving into the world of Windows domains and enterprise-style networks.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>eJPT: My Experience</title><link>https://vksundararajan.github.io/buffor.lol/blog/ejpt-my-experience/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vksundararajan.github.io/buffor.lol/blog/ejpt-my-experience/</guid><description>&lt;p>Hey everyone,&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I’m super excited to share that I’ve passed the &lt;mark>eJPT exam&lt;/mark> with a score of &lt;strong>94% in my first attempt&lt;/strong>. I managed to finish it in 6 hours, and I’ve got some handy tips and personal insights that might help those of you gearing up for the same challenge.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:4800/format:webp/1*x9qSy2pnIywruzaCBBfLQg.png" alt="eJPT">&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="a-little-bit-about-me">A Little Bit About Me&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Before jumping into the specifics, let me give you a bit of background. I’ve been a &lt;strong>software developer&lt;/strong> for three years, but I had zero experience in penetration testing before this. However, I decided to give it a shot and prepped for about two months. This goes to show that anyone can master this with the right focus and dedication.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>