<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Buffor // Books</title><link>https://buffor.lol/</link><description>Recent content on Buffor // Books</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://buffor.lol/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>TryHackMe Writeup — Brains</title><link>https://buffor.lol/blog/thm-brains/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://buffor.lol/blog/thm-brains/</guid><description>&lt;p>Room Link: &lt;a href="https://tryhackme.com/room/brains">https://tryhackme.com/room/brains&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="1-red-exploit-the-server">1. Red: Exploit the Server!&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;code>The city forgot to close its gate. Welcome to the Brains challenge, part of TryHackMe’s Hackathon! All brains gathered to build an engineering marvel; however, it seems strangers had found away to get in.&lt;/code>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://github.com/vksundararajan/Amaigai/blob/main/Brains/1.png?raw=true" alt="Image">&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As the &lt;strong>Ping&lt;/strong> output shows, the TTL (Time to Live) value was 63. This is a strong indicator that the target machine was running a Linux distribution. With this information in hand, I proceeded to port scanning using &lt;strong>nmap&lt;/strong> to discover open services.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Behind the Prompts: What I Learned from Engineering LLM Prompts</title><link>https://buffor.lol/blog/behind-the-prompts-what-i-learned-from-engineering-llm-prompts/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:55:40 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://buffor.lol/blog/behind-the-prompts-what-i-learned-from-engineering-llm-prompts/</guid><description>&lt;p>Over the last 2 days, I’ve dived deep into &lt;mark>Prompt Engineering&lt;/mark> — not the surface-level prompt crafting, but the core architecture of how LLMs interpret, generate, and optimise responses based on prompt structure and configuration.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>What started as a casual exploration through &lt;strong>Google’s Prompt Engineering Essentials&lt;/strong> turned into an unexpectedly technical journey that bridged NLP design, token sampling, inference configuration, and agent-based reasoning.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Let’s break it down.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="llms-are-not-magical--theyre-token-predictors">LLMs Are Not Magical — They&amp;rsquo;re Token Predictors&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Large Language Models, whether GPT, Gemini, Claude, or Llama, are not creative writers — they are statistical machines that &lt;strong>predict the next token given the previous context&lt;/strong>. That’s all.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Beyond Bugs and Pipelines: Source Code Review Intelligence</title><link>https://buffor.lol/blog/beyond-bugs-and-pipelines-source-code-review-intelligence/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://buffor.lol/blog/beyond-bugs-and-pipelines-source-code-review-intelligence/</guid><description>&lt;p>In today’s software landscape, security is less about gates and more about gradients. It’s no longer enough to write secure code — we must think about how that code emerges, how it&amp;rsquo;s validated, and how it evolves.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Over the past months, I’ve delved into both dimensions: the theory and execution of a Secure Software Development Life Cycle (S-SDLC), and the manual + automated art of Source Code Review. But the synergy between the two isn’t well documented.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>TryHackMe Writeup — Billing</title><link>https://buffor.lol/blog/thm-billing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://buffor.lol/blog/thm-billing/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;code>Some mistakes can be costly. Gain a shell, find the way and escalate your privileges! Bruteforcing is out of scope for this room.&lt;/code>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Room Link: &lt;a href="https://tryhackme.com/room/billing">https://tryhackme.com/room/billing&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="1-enumeration">1. Enumeration&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/vickie-ks/Amaigai/refs/heads/main/Billing/1.png" alt="1">&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Identifying whether a target machine operates on &lt;u>Linux&lt;/u> can be facilitated by examining the TTL (Time to Live) value during a ping test. A TTL value of 63 typically indicates a Linux system, enabling a more tailored enumeration strategy that is.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/vickie-ks/Amaigai/refs/heads/main/Billing/2.png" alt="2">&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>CRTP: My Experience</title><link>https://buffor.lol/blog/crtp-my-experience/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://buffor.lol/blog/crtp-my-experience/</guid><description>&lt;p>Hey everyone,&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I’m really happy to share that I’ve cleared the &lt;mark>CRTP (Certified Red Team Professional)&lt;/mark> exam &lt;strong>on my first attempt!&lt;/strong> This was a whole new area for me—no prior Active Directory (AD) pentesting experience, and still, I managed to get through it. So if you’re someone wondering whether this cert is possible without an AD background—yes, it is. Let me walk you through how I did it.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/628794_3744024c76874b21808fcc3765e6f663~mv2.png" alt="certified-red-team-professional-crtp">&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="my-background-before-crtp">My Background Before CRTP&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Before jumping into CRTP, my only real exposure to pentesting was TryHackMe rooms and clearing the eJPT exam. To be honest, I had never done any complete AD-based CTFs before. CRTP was the first time I was diving into the world of Windows domains and enterprise-style networks.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>eJPT: My Experience</title><link>https://buffor.lol/blog/ejpt-my-experience/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://buffor.lol/blog/ejpt-my-experience/</guid><description>&lt;p>Hey everyone,&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I’m super excited to share that I’ve passed the &lt;mark>eJPT exam&lt;/mark> with a score of &lt;strong>94% in my first attempt&lt;/strong>. I managed to finish it in 6 hours, and I’ve got some handy tips and personal insights that might help those of you gearing up for the same challenge.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:4800/format:webp/1*x9qSy2pnIywruzaCBBfLQg.png" alt="eJPT">&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="a-little-bit-about-me">A Little Bit About Me&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Before jumping into the specifics, let me give you a bit of background. I’ve been a &lt;strong>software developer&lt;/strong> for three years, but I had zero experience in penetration testing before this. However, I decided to give it a shot and prepped for about two months. This goes to show that anyone can master this with the right focus and dedication.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>